<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Commemorate</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
<string name="s1">We are committed to providing flexible and cost to bring real value and return on our clients effective solutions. Through proven technology by bringing together talent, we help our clients make measurable improvements in web design, search engine optimization and systems integration business.</string>
<string name="s2">We really like to see themselves as a unique network of institutions. First, we insist that we do best - web design! Unlike many of our competitors, we resist the temptation, to the development of the traditional marketing agency focused on the remaining web design. We are in what we do well, but most importantly, we know how to translate into successful strategies for our clients knowledge of our site!</string>
<string name="s3">Our industry is often polarized by two different types of suppliers. At one extreme, you have a boutique marketing firms and design agencies, to meet the big brands. These people can only large companies with deep pockets to match the project. Is rare, even considering these institutions less than 5 million project. You have hundreds of features of the spectrum are small-scale operations, one band, one-way student and part-time designers on the other side. These enterprises often lack the depth, experience or expertise to help develop and implement effective online strategies, and their customers.</string>
<string name="s4">WebInfoways is one of the few network services spectrum, one of the two sides. For large enterprises, we have the ability to weaken, but without compromising the quality of our work in the price of large organizations. For small businesses, we can not blow the budget to provide the same quality of service! Have the most talented people in the industry fifty work for us, we have the resources and expertise to inspire confidence, no matter your business size or scope of your project.</string>


</resources>